<blogs>
    <section>
        <id>posture1116</id>
        <title>Why posture is crucial to your health!</title>
        <para>Here at Elevate Health &amp; Fitness, one of the first things we do is assess your posture. Why is this so important? Well, posture not only plays a significant role in how efficiently you move, but also in relation to your overall health</para>
        <para>I’m sure you’ve all thought about your posture at one point or another, trying to stand up straighter or sit more ergonomically, indeed, I remember being told by my parents to ‘stand up straight’ and I now find myself repeating this to my kids!</para>
        <para>So what is posture? Well, Paul Chek defines posture as:</para>
        <para><cite>‘The position from which movement begins and ends’
        with ideal posture being:
        ‘That state of muscular and skeletal balance, which protects the supporting structures of the body against injury or progressive deformity, irrespective of the attitude in which these structures are working or resting. It is during a state of ideal posture that the muscles will function most efficiently’.
        </cite></para>
        <para>If you have poor posture, it negatively effects how you look and feel, overloading your muscles, joints and tendons, often leading to pain and injury if not addressed. The rest of your body is also affected as your internal organs are not optimally supported and your circulation and breathing becomes impaired, fostering an environment for disease and dysfunction.</para>
        <para>Indeed, if the exercise program you are following does not address your posture, this can potentially lead to disastrous and expensive consequences. Detrimental results of poorly designed, inappropriate exercise programs include but are not limited to: muscle imbalance, nerve entrapment, altered biomechanics, increased pressure on nerve roots, damage to joint capsules and inert structures, increased risk of injury to muscles, ligaments and tendons, poor neuromuscular control, altered movement patterns, faulty motor engram development, overall dysfunction and pain.</para>
        <para>Improving and maintaining your ideal posture allows your body to be optimally aligned, with your muscles in balance, whilst also creating the optimal conditions for all the systems of your body to work effectively, with benefits including:
            <ul>
                <li>Reduced chance of injury due to less stress on joints, ligaments, tendons and muscles.</li>
                <li>Improved performance in not only your chosen sport, but also in your work and day to day activities, as your body will move more efficiently, with better balance and increased ability to generate force and movement.</li>
                <li>You will also look and feel better with an ideal posture, improving your self-confidence and overall well-being!</li>
            </ul>
        </para>
        <para>So, as you can see, posture is very important and this is why here at Elevate Health &amp; Fitness we not only assess you at the beginning of your journey, we also ensure your programs are designed to improve and help you maintain your optimal posture, with further regular assessments to ensure you are on the right track!</para>
        <para>If you would like us to help you improve your posture, whatever your health and fitness goals are, please do not hesitate to contact us for a free, no obligation consultation and let us help you to Elevate your health!</para>
    </section>
    <section>
        <id>testpic</id>
        <title>Test</title>
        <para>Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test </para><para>Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test </para><para>Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test </para><para>Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test Test </para>
    </section>
    <section>
        <id>Twat</id>
        <title>Testing again</title>
        <para>Paragraph 1</para>
        <para>Paragraph 2</para>
        <para>Paragraph 3</para>
        <para>Paragraph 4</para>
        <para>Paragraph 1</para>
        <para>Paragraph 1</para>
    </section>
</blogs>
